Pauline Frederick Papers, 1917-1990
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series I. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
  - NBC
    - Programs
      - "Today Show", [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 13)
        - Correspondence, publicity, and weekly mail reports, 1967-70 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence (audience response), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - "UN Under Fire": transcript, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - UNESCO 25th Anniversary special: transcripts, schedules and correspondence, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - UN 10th and 20th anniversaries: correspondence, press releases, and script, 1955, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - "Weekday" (radio): transcript, Apr 1956 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - "What Risk Retaliation?": correspondence and script, Mar 1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous broadcasts, programs, and proposals: correspondence and scripts, 1955-75, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence
      - Contracts, employment material, and expenses, 1956-65 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Interoffice and miscellaneous, 1953-75, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - William McAndrew (includes reports to him), 1953-67 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Publicity, [see also individual programs]
      - "Inside NBC News," 1957-67 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - "NBC Biography," 1954-72 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - "NBC Feature," 1954-61 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - "NBC Radio Network News," 1953-60 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-64, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIAL] (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Notes
      - "The Reporter," "UN World," and "Men in Glass Houses," undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-68, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous interviews, 1971, undated, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Appeal to U Thant on behalf of captured correspondents: correspondence and notes, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Women's Committee vs. NBC: correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Subject files
      - China: wire copies and notes, 1955-71, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Congo: memoranda, wire copies, and notes, 1960-61 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Cuba: wire copies and notes, 1960-61 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Guinea: wire copies, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Dag Hammarskjold
        - Press conferences, 1953-61 (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
        - Notes, wire copies, clippings, and correspondence, 1957-62 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Middle East: memoranda, wire copies, and notes, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Soviet Union: notes, and press releases, 1960-67 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Adlai Stevenson: wire copies, notes, press releases, speeches, interview, correspondence, and memorabilia, 1961-65 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - U Thant: wire copies, notes, and press conferences, 1965-66 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - United Nations budget: notes, 1961, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Vietnam: notes, wire copies, press conferences, and memoranda, 1965-72 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Tours (official)
      - SABENA (Belgian Air Lines) Press Tour: correspondence, itineraries, and Press Club Book, Nov 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Trip with Dag Hammarskjold to Rome, Cairo, Hungary: correspondence, Nov 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Japan Airlines Inaugural Flight: memorabilia and correspondence, May 1959 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - UN Correspondents' visit to Canada: itinerary, notes, and correspondence, May 1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Adlai Stevenson trip to Latin America, Jun 1961
        - Notes (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, cables, and wire copies (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - Itineraries and miscellaneous information for correspondents (Box 16, Folder 11)
        - Memorabilia (Box 16, Folder 12)
        - Speeches and statements by others (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
        - Related interviews (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Ethiopia: passenger list and clipping, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - UN correspondents' trip to Germany: correspondence and itineraries, Apr-May 1963 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Foreign correspondents: itineraries, publicity, correspondence, and scripts, 1964-73 (Box 17, Folder 1-13)
      - Memorabilia, 1959, 1974, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - National Public Radio
    - News and miscellaneous broadcasts (includes "Closer Look," "Special Reports," interviews, and broadcasts from the Council on Foreign Relations): scripts and related material
      - 1975-78 (Box 17, Folder 15-17)
      - 1979-81 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Programs
      - "All Things Considered"
        - Broadcasts, 1975-79, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
        - Correspondence and publicity, 1975-77 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Connecticut Public TV inaugural broadcast: correspondence and publicity, Jun 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - "Focus: Women in Developing Countries": notes, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - "National Round Table": correspondence and script, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - "National Town Meeting": correspondence, script, and publicity, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - "Options" (Henry Kissinger documentary): script and correspondence, 1976, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - "Over Easy": publicity, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - "Pauline Frederick and Colleagues"
        - Proposal, publicity, and program lists, 1976-79 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Scripts, transcripts, and related material
          - Jan-Apr 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
          - May 1977-Jun 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1-10)
      - Presidential debates, 1976
        - Publicity (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Transcript (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Scrapbook, "Second Presidential Debate" (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - "World Chronicle": notes, scripts, and correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Program standards and practices, 1973, 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Press conferences, 1976-77 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1975-80 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Contracts, expenses, and salary projections, 1975-80 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and interoffice memos, 1975-79 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Publicity, 1973-77 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Other Activities
    - American University Board of Trustees
      - Correspondence, 1962-82 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Printed material, 1973-78 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-83 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - American Women in Radio and TV (AWRT): correspondence, newsletter, convention programs, and press releases, 1952-80 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Association of Radio-TV News Analysts: correspondence and minutes, 1962-77 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace: correspondence, 1974-75 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Committee to Evaluate the National News Council: correspondence and meeting agenda, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - The Correspondents Fund: correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc.: correspondence, agenda, and notes, 1971-85 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Crisis to Crisis (Advisory Board): correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Dairy Society International (narrated "Small World"): correspondence, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dupont Award presenter: correspondence, scripts, and publicity, 1973, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Policy Association: correspondence and printed material, 1965-84, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Franklin Mint, Medallic Yearbook Advisory Panel and Family Library Board: correspondence, printed material, 1973-84 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - International Exchange Students Conference (re: U Thant address arranged by PF): correspondence, printed material, and speech, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - International Radio and TV Society: correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - National Committee on US-China Relations: correspondence, 1976-80 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Overseas Press Club of America: correspondence, Bulletin, and printed material, 1952-84 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tower Fellow (University of Bridgeport): correspondence membership lists, and notes, 1981-83 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - United Nations Association: correspondence, agenda, and clippings, 1973-77 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - United Nations Correspondents Association (UNCA)
      - Correspondence, 1959-81 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Honorary luncheons and parties: correspondence, notes, clippings, publicity, and reservation lists
        - Nikolai Fedorenko, 1963, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 21, Folder 15)
        - Dag Hammarskjold, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - Luis Moreno-Verdin, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 17)
        - Head of Missions of the UN, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 18)
        - Presidents of the General Assembly, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Christian Herter, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - Fidel Castro, 1959, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - American Newspaper Guild, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Economic Survey of UN correspondents by Otto Leichter: correspondence and reports, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Press Wireless, Inc.: correspondence, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Committee on Constitutional Matters: notes, correspondence and recommendations, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee: correspondence, agenda, and notes, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Dag Hammarskjold Memorial Scholarship: memoranda and publicity, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - UN Correspondent: correspondence, notes, and issues, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - TV program proposal: correspondence and script, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Election as president: congratulatory correspondence, memos, publicity, ballot tallies, and notes, 1958-59 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Request for relief from Foreign Agents Registration Act (mail censorship): correspondence, printed material, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1958-81 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Voice of America Panel to Study the Role of Foreign News Correspondents: publicity and correspondence, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - "Woman to Woman" (TV program): correspondence and publicity, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Women's National Press Club: correspondence and newsletter, 1958-68 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - World Survival Through UN Reform (United Nations Association of Los Angeles): transcript, 1980, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - WRUF Broadcasting Day: correspondence and memoranda, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous organizations (A-Z), 1942-84 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous special dinners, luncheons, and panels, 1954-85 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Speeches and Events
    - Texts (includes undated fragments and notes), [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - 1945-63 (Box 23, Folder 1-14)
      - 1964-71 (Box 24, Folder 1-8)
      - 1972-77 (Box 25, Folder 1-7)
      - 1978-83, undated (Box 26, Folder 1-7)
      - unidentified and miscellaneous notes (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence and publicity, [see also oversize materials]
      - 1931-60 (Box 27, Folder 3-17)
      - 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
      - 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
      - Women at the White House Conference on International Cooperation, 30 Nov 1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - 1965 (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
      - Asian-American Women Broadcasters Conference, 17 May 1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
      - Southeastern Hospital Conference, 3 May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - 1967-68 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
      - 1969-71 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
      - San Diego State College Commencement speech, 8 Jun 1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
      - Pacem in Terris III, 8-11 Oct 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - 1973-76 (Box 32, Folder 1-7)
      - 1977-85, undated (Box 33, Folder 1-10)
    - Agents and speakers bureaus: correspondence, publicity, 1948-82 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Itineraries and schedules, 1948-66, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963-80 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Cancelled or refused engagements: correspondence, 1947-84 (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
  - Writings
    - Newspaper columns
      - "Women in Official Life"
        - Typescripts and clippings, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - "Women of Diplomacy"
        - Promotion, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Typescripts and clippings, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
        - Correspondence, 1931-32 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Uncle Sam's Diary, "issued weekly under the auspices of the United States Society, Washington," 3 Nov 1931-25 Jan 1937 (incomplete) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - America Prepares for Tomorrow: The Story of Our Total Defense Effort, by P. Frederick and others: memos, typescripts, correspondence, review, and photocopy of portions written by P. Frederick, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - "Man Against Fear" (Dag Hammarskjold): typescripts and notes, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Articles, typescripts, printed items, and related correspondence
      - U.S. News, 1934-37 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1937-50, undated (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1933-85, undated (Box 35, Folder 6-12)
      - General correspondence, 1932-79 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
    - "The United Nations: Option for Survival," The Georgia Review, Vol. XXXIV, No. 2 (Summer 1980): correspondence, text, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ten First Ladies of the World, Meredith Press, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Typescripts (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence
        - Meredith Press, 1964-70 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Research, 1965-66 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Fan mail, 1967-74 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Promotion: publicity, reviews, 1967-68 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Professional
    - Letters from listeners and fans
      - 1940-62 (Box 36, Folder 10-15)
      - 1963-85, undated (Box 37, Folder 1-12)
    - Invitations
      - White House, 1936-71 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-84 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Oral history projects
      - Broadcast Pioneers Library, 1976-84 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - United Nations, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - "Declaration of Interdependence," 1974-75 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - With notable persons
      - Alexander Kerensky, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Edward R. Murrow, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Carl Sandburg, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Marlene Sanders, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Adlai Stevenson, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - U Thant, 1965-74 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Kurt Waldheim, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-85 (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
  - Personal
    - Friends
      - To Ann Cordell, 1951-63 (Box 38, Folder 15-17)
      - From Madge Crump, 1967-76, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-83, undated (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
      - Marriage to Charles Robbins, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Knee injury: get well letters and enclosed clippings, 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Family
      - Charles Robbins, 1968-77 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Other relatives, especially sister Catharine Crowding, 1938-80 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Business
    - Catharine Crowding, 1945-46 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - General, 1957-83 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series III. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL
  - Articles and Clippings
    - 1941-69 (Box 39, Folder 9-12)
    - 1970-90, undated (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
  - Diaries and Appointment Calendars
    - 1940-79 (Box 40, Folder 4-9)
    - 1980-84 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Memorabilia
    - General, 1925-80 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbooks
      - "Pauline Frederick Robbins at 70," undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Key Biscayne Chamber of Commerce Spring Banquet, 31 Mar 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - School and College Material
    - Grammar school (Harrisburg, PA): grades and essays, 1917-19 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Thomas A. Edison Junior High School (Harrisburg, PA)
      - Compositions, clippings, and memorabilia, 1921-23 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Edison Record (PF an editor), 1921-23 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Central High School (Harrisburg, PA)
      - Clippings, course papers, and correspondence, 1923-26 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - The Mid-Year Buzz (PF editor in chief), 1924, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Argus (PF associate editor), 1924-26 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - American University
      - The American Eagle (PF associate editor), 1926-30 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Grades, course papers, and memorabilia 1926-30 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1926-39 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Aucola (yearbook), 1926-30 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, 1926-30 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - "The Effect of Decisions by Courts of the States of the Union on the International Relations of the U.S." (master's thesis), 1931 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Awards
    - Theta Sigma Phi Headliner Award, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Soroptimist Society of Harrisburg honorary membership, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - duPont Award, 1954, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Publicity (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Fan mail (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Program and speech (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Peabody Award, 1955, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Publicity (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Speech (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - McCall's Mike Award, 1956, 1961, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Radio-Television Daily Woman of the Year, 1956, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia Club of Advertising Women Outstanding Woman of 1956 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Amvets Woman of the Year, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Honorable Order of Kentucky Colonels, 1961, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Gallup Poll "ten women most admired by Americans," 1961, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - United Nations Award of the Deadline Club of New York, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - University of Missouri Honor Award for Distinguished Service in Journalism, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - National Father's Day Committee Woman of the Year, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Advertising Association of the West Award, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - AAUW Woman of the Year, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Alpha Epsilon Rho honorary membership, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Downtown St. Louis, Inc. National Outstanding Working Woman, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Detroit Central Business District Association, Salute to Women Who Work Award, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - American Academy of Achievement Award, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Theta Sigma Chi Woman of the Year, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Award for Excellence in Journalism, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - University of Southern California Journalism Achievement Award, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Westchester County (New York) Federation of Women's Clubs Annual Woman of the Year, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - YWCA Centennial Medal, 1969, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Deadline Club Hall of Fame, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - American Women in Radio and Television Woman of the Year, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - American Women in Radio and TV, Silver Satellite Award, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Paul White Award, 1980, [see also AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - Correspondence and speech (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Fan mail (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Publicity (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Women in Communications Matrix Award, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - American University: Mortar Board Fellow, 1980, and The President's Circle, charter member, 1981-82 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Living Legacy Award, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous: certificates, publicity, and correspondence, 1945-80 (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
  - Honorary Degrees
    - Lycoming College, 1956, [see also PHOTOGRAPHS and OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - American University, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Mt. Holyoke College, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Gettysburg College, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Beaver College, 1962, [see PHOTOGRAPHS] (Box 45)
    - Lindenwood College, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - St. Francis College, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Ohio Northern University, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Denison University, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Russell Sage College, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Boston University, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - William Jewell College, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Ohio University (Athens), 1965, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Bates College, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - University of Portland, 1969, [see also OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Keuka College, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Manhattan College, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Wayne State University, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Lebanon Valley College, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - St. Olaf College, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Bucknell University, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Lehigh University, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - DePauw University, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - University of Bridgeport, 1985, [see also PHOTOGRAPHS] (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Series IV. PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Professional Activities, [See Appendix for alphabetical list of photos of individuals]
    - Freelance, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - NBC Radio, 1938-45 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - War Correspondent, Jun-Jul 1945
      - Ceylon [Sri Lanka] (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Flying the "Hump" of the Himalayas (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - China (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - India (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Italy (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Middle East (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Europe, 1945-46
      - Belgium (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Denmark (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - France (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Germany (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Poland (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - ABC
      - Programs: convention coverage and interviews, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Tours
        - Uruguay, for inauguration of President Berretta, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - U.S. Navy trip to Hawaii, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Berlin Airlift, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Interviews, 1949, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Promotion
        - Radio stations, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Portraits, 1951, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-52, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - NBC
      - Programs
        - Convention coverage, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - "Meet the Press," 1965, 1967, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous: "Africa: 5 Minutes to 12" through "Today," 1953-68 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Publicity, 1953-85, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Tours
        - SABENA, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Japan Airlines, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Adlai Stevenson's trip to Latin America, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - Ethiopia, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - UN and foreign correspondents, 1963-73 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous broadcasts, interviews and events
        - Officals and colleagues, 1954-73, undated (Box 48, Folder 6-7)
        - United Nations, 1963, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Receptions, 1965, 1972, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - At work, 1956-75, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - National Public Radio
      - Programs
        - Presidential debates, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - "World Chronicle," 1980-81 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Speeches and events
      - 1954 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - UN Correspondents Association (UNCA), 1959 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - 1959 (Box 49, Folder 9)